<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>org.kde.kile</id>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="ar">كايل</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="ca-valencia">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="cs">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="da">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="de">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="el">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="en-GB">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="et">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="eu">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="fi">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="fr">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="gl">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="ia">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="id">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="it">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="ka">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="ko">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="pl">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt-BR">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="ru">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="sk">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="sl">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="tr">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Kile</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKilexx</name>
  <name xml:lang="zh-CN">Kile</name>
  <summary>TeX/LaTeX Editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ar">محرّر تخ/لاتخ</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca">Editor de TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ca-valencia">Editor de TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="cs">Editor pro TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="de">TeX-/LaTeX-Editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="el">Επεξεργαστής TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="en-GB">TeX/LaTeX Editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Editor TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="et">TeX/LaTeXi redaktor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="eu">TeX/LaTeX editorea</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fi">TeX/LaTeX-muokkain</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="fr">Éditeur TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="gl">Editor de TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ia">Editor de TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="id">Editor TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="it">Editor TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ka">TeX/LaTeX რედაქტორი</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="ko">TeX/LaTeX 편집기</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">TeX/LaTeX-bewerker</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pl">Edytor TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">Editor de TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt-BR">Editor TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sk">TeX/LaTeX Editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sl">Urejevalnik TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">Tex/Latex-editor</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="tr">TeX/LaTeX Düzenleyici</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Редактор TeX/LaTeX</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxTeX/LaTeX Editorxx</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="zh-CN">TeX/LaTeX 编辑器</summary>
  <description>
    <p>
      Kile is a user-friendly TeX/LaTeX editor by KDE. Kile gives you the ability to use all the functionality of LaTeX in a graphical interface and has interactive preview mechanisms to readily see the results of editing.
    </p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">El Kile és un editor TeX/LaTeX fàcil d'emprar fet per la comunitat KDE. El Kile proporciona la possibilitat d'usar totes les funcionalitats del LaTeX en una interfície gràfica i té mecanismes de previsualització interactius per a veure immediatament els resultats de l'edició.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Kile és un editor TeX/LaTeX fàcil d'emprar fet per la comunitat KDE. Kile proporciona la possibilitat d'utilitzar totes les funcionalitats de LaTeX en una interfície gràfica i té mecanismes de previsualització interactius per a veure immediatament els resultats de l'edició.</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Kile ist ein benutzerfreundlicher TeX/LaTeX-Editor von KDE. Kile gibt Ihnen die Möglichkeit, die gesamte Funktionalität von LaTeX in einer grafischen Oberfläche zu nutzen und verfügt über interaktive Vorschaumechanismen, um die Ergebnisse der Bearbeitung zu sehen.</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Το Kile είναι ένας φιλικός προς στον χρήστη επεξεργαστής TeX/LaTeX από το KDE. Το Kile σάς δίνει τη δυνατότητα να χρησιμοποιήσετε όλη τη λειτουργικότητα του LaTeX σε ένα γραφικό περιβάλλον και περιέχει διαδραστικούς μηχανισμούς προεπισκόπησης για να βλέπετε άμεσα τα αποτελέσματα της επεξεργασίας.</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Kile is a user-friendly TeX/LaTeX editor by KDE. Kile gives you the ability to use all the functionality of LaTeX in a graphical interface and has interactive preview mechanisms to readily see the results of editing.</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Kile es un editor de TeX/LaTeX amigable creado por KDE. Kile le permite usar toda la funcionalidad de LaTeX mediante una interfaz gráfica y posee mecanismos interactivos de vista previa para comprobar rápidamente el resultado de la edición.</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Kile on KDE kasutajasõbralik TeX/LaTeXi redaktor. See võimaldab kasutada kõiki LaTeXi võimalusi graafilises liideses ning pakub interaktiivseid viise kiiresti näha oma redigeerimise tulemusi.</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Kile KDEren TeX/LaTeX editore erabilerraza da. Kilek LaTeX-en funtzionalitate guztiak interfaze grafiko batean erabiltzeko gaitasuna ematen dizu, eta aurreikuspegi mekanismo elkarreragileak ditu edizioaren emaitzak erraz ikusteko.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Kile on KDE:n käyttäjäystävällinen TeX/LaTeX-muokkain. Kilellä saat kaikki LaTeXin toiminnot graafiseen käyttöliittymään, jonka vuorovaikutteisuus auttaa sinua näkemään muokkauksen tulokset.</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Kile est un éditeur TeX/LaTeX intuitif par KDE. Kile vous offre la possibilité d'utiliser toutes les fonctionnalités de LaTeX au sein d'une interface graphique et dispose de mécanismes d'aperçu interactifs qui vous permettent d'afficher les résultats de l'édition.</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Kile é un editor de TeX e LaTeX fácil de usar creado por KDE. Kile permítelle usar toda a funcionalidade de LaTeX nunha interface gráfica e ten un mecanismo de vista previa para ver rapidamente os resultados da edición.</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Kile adalah editor TeX/LaTeX yang mudah digunakan oleh KDE. Kile memberi Anda kemampuan untuk menggunakan semua fungsi LaTeX dalam antarmuka grafis dan memiliki mekanisme pratinjau interaktif untuk kesiapan melihat hasil pengeditan.</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Kile è un editor TeX/LaTeX della comunità KDE facile da usare. Ti dà la possibilità di utilizzare tutte la funzionalità di LaTeX in un'interfaccia grafica e dispone di un meccanismo di anteprima interattiva per vedere prontamente i risultati della modifica.</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">Kile은 KDE의 TeX/LaTeX 편집기입니다. Kile을 사용하여 그래픽 환경에서 LaTeX 기능을 활용할 수 있으며 편집 결과를 즉시 볼 수 있는 미리 보기를 제공합니다.</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Kile is een gebruikersvriendelijke TeX/LaTeX bewerker door KDE. Kile geeft u de mogelijkheid om alle functionaliteit van LaTeX in een grafisch interface te gebruiken en heeft interactieve voorbeeldweergave om op een redelijke manier het resultaat van de bewerking te zien.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Kile jest przyjaznym użytkownikowi edytorem TeX/LaTeX dla KDE. Kile umożliwia wykorzystanie wszystkich możliwości LaTeX przy użyciu interfejsu graficznego i ma mechanizm interaktywnego podglądu, aby szybko podejrzeć wyniki edycji.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">O Kile é um editor amigável de TeX/LaTeX para o KDE. O Kile dá-lhe a capacidade de usar todas as funcionalidades do LaTeX numa interface gráfica e tem mecanismos de antevisão interactiva para ler de forma imediata os resultados da edição.</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">O Kile é um editor de TeX/LaTeX fácil de usar criado pela comunidade KDE. Ele permite usar toda a funcionalidade do LaTeX com uma interface gráfica, possuindo ainda pré-visualização interative para ver dinamicamente os resultados da sua edição.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Kile je užívateľsky príjemný editor TeX/LaTeX od KDE. Kile vám dáva možnosť používať všetky funkcie LaTeXu v grafickom rozhraní a má interaktívne mechanizmy náhľadu, aby ste mohli okamžite vidieť výsledky úprav.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Kile je uporabniku prijazen TeX/LaTeX urejevalnik na namizju KDE. Kile omogoča uporabo vseh funkcij LaTeX v grafičnem vmesniku in imainteraktivne predogledne mehanizmi za lažji ogled rezultatov urejanja.</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Kile är en användarvänlig Tex- och Latex-editor av KDE. Kile ger dig möjlighet att använda hela Latex funktionalitet i ett grafiskt gränssnitt, och har en interaktiv förhandsgranskningsmekanism för att enkelt kunna se redigeringsresultatet.</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Kile, KDE tarafından yapılan kullanıcı dostu bir TeX/LaTeX düzenleyicisidir. Kile, LaTeX'in tüm işlevselliğini grafik bir arabirimde kullanmanıza izin verir ve düzenlemenizin sonuçlarını anında görebilmeniz için etkileşimli önizleme mekanizmaları sunar.</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Kile — дружня до користувача програма для редагування коду TeX/LaTeX від KDE. Kile надає вам змогу скористатися усіма функціональними можливостями LaTeX за допомогою графічного інтерфейсу та має механізми інтерактивного попереднього перегляду для негайного отримання результатів редагування.</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxKile is a user-friendly TeX/LaTeX editor by KDE. Kile gives you the ability to use all the functionality of LaTeX in a graphical interface and has interactive preview mechanisms to readily see the results of editing.xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">Kile 是一款 KDE 开发的 TeX/LaTeX 编辑器。Kile 能够让您在图形界面中使用 LaTeX 的所有功能，并且拥有交互式预览机制以便随时查看编辑结果。</p>
    <p>Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ar">الميزات:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ca-valencia">Característiques:</p>
    <p xml:lang="cs">Vlastnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="da">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="de">Funktionen:</p>
    <p xml:lang="el">Χαρακτηριστικά:</p>
    <p xml:lang="en-GB">Features:</p>
    <p xml:lang="es">Funciones:</p>
    <p xml:lang="et">Omadused:</p>
    <p xml:lang="eu">Ezaugarria:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fi">Ominaisuudet:</p>
    <p xml:lang="fr">Fonctionnalités :</p>
    <p xml:lang="gl">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ia">Characteristicas:</p>
    <p xml:lang="id">Fitur:</p>
    <p xml:lang="it">Caratteristiche:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ka">თვისებები:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ko">기능:</p>
    <p xml:lang="nl">Kenmerken:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pl">Możliwości:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt">Funcionalidades:</p>
    <p xml:lang="pt-BR">Recursos:</p>
    <p xml:lang="ru">Возможности:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sk">Funkcie:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sl">Zmožnosti:</p>
    <p xml:lang="sv">Funktioner:</p>
    <p xml:lang="tr">Özellikler:</p>
    <p xml:lang="uk">Можливості:</p>
    <p xml:lang="x-test">xxFeatures:xx</p>
    <p xml:lang="zh-CN">程序功能：</p>
    <ul>
      <li>Compile, convert and view your document with one click</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">صرّف مستنداتك وحوّلها واعرضها بنقرة واحدة</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Compila, converteix i mostra el document amb un clic</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Compila, convertix i mostra el document amb un clic</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Dokumente mit einem Klick kompilieren, umwandeln und anzeigen</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Μεταγλώττιση, μετατροπή και προβολή των εγγράφων σας με ένα κλικ</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Compile, convert and view your document with one click</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Compile, convierta y visualice documentos con un solo clic</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Dokumendi kompileerimine, teisendamine ja vaatamine üheainsa klõpsuga</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Konpilatu, bihurtu eta ikusi zure dokumentua klik bakarrarekin</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Käännä, muunna ja näytä tiedostosi yhdellä napsautuksella</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Compiler, convertir et afficher vos documents en un clic</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Compilar, converter e visualizar o documento cun clic.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Compila, converte e vide ty documento con un click</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Kompilasi, konversi, dan lihat dokumen Anda dengan satu klik</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Compila, converte e visualizza i tuoi documenti con un clic</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">문서를 간단하게 컴파일, 변환, 보기</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Compileert, converteert en toont uw document met één klik</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Kompiluj, przekształcaj i oglądaj swoje dokumenty na kliknięcie</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Compilar, converter e ver o seu documento com um 'click'</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Compile, converta e visualize seu documento com apenas um clique</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Zostavte, skonvertujte a zobrazte dokument jedným kliknutím</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Prevod, pretvorba in ogled dokumenta z enim klikom</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Kompilera, konvertera och visa dokumentet med ett klick</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Tek tıklama ile belgenizi derleyin, dönüştürün ve görüntüleyin</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Збирання, перетворення та перегляд документів у одне клацання кнопкою миші.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCompile, convert and view your document with one clickxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">一键对您的文档进行编译、转换和查看</li>
      <li>Auto-completion of (La)TeX commands</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">إكمال آليّ لأوامر (لا)تخ</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Compleció automàtica d'ordres del (La)TeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Compleció automàtica d'ordres del (La)TeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Automatische Vervollständigung von (La)TeX-Befehlen</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Αυτόματη συμπλήρωση των εντολών του (La)TeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Auto-completion of (La)TeX commands</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Terminación automática de órdenes de (La)TeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">(La)TeXi käskude automaatne lõpetamine</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">(La)Tex komandoen osatze automatikoa</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Täydennä (La)TeX-komennot automaattisesti</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Auto-complètement des balises (La)TeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Completación automática de ordes de (La)TeX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Auto-completion de commandos de (La)TeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Penyelesaian otomatis perintah-perintah (La)TeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Completamento automatico dei comandi (La)TeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">(La)TeX -ის ბრძანებების ავტომატური დასრულება</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">(La)TeX 명령 자동 완성</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Automatische aanvulling van (La)TeX commando's</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Samouzupełnianie poleceń (La)TeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Completação automática de comandos de (La)TeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Função de auto-completar para comandos do (La)TeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Automatické dokončenie príkazov (La)TeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Avtomatsko dokončevanje (La)TeX ukazov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Automatisk komplettering av Tex- och Latex-kommandon</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">(La)TeX komutlarının Otomatik Tamamlanması</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Автодоповнення команд (La)TeX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAuto-completion of (La)TeX commandsxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">(La)TeX 命令自动补全</li>
      <li>Templates and wizards make starting new documents very little work</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">تجعل القوالب والمُرشدات بدء المستندات الجديدة مهمّة سهلة</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Les plantilles i els assistents fan que sigui molt poca feina iniciar els documents nous</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Les plantilles i els assistents fan que siga molt poca faena iniciar els documents nous</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Vorlagen und Assistenten helfen beim Erstellen neuer Dokumente</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Τα πρότυπα και οι βοηθοί απλοποιούν τη διαδικασία έναρξης νέων εγγράφων</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Templates and wizards make starting new documents very little work</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Plantillas y asistentes para facilitar la creación de nuevos documentos</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Mallid ja nõustajad lubavad muretult luua uusi dokumente</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Txantiloiek eta morroiek dokumentu berriekin hastea asko errazten dute</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Aloita uusi tiedosto helposti mallipohjien ja opastettujen toimintojen avulla</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Modèles et assistants pour créer de nouveaux documents en très peu de temps</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Modelos e asistentes para facilitar o inicio de novos documentos.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Template dan asisten membuat pemulaian dokumen baru sangat sedikit bekerja</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">I modelli e le procedure guidate ti fanno iniziare i nuovi documenti con pochissimo lavoro</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">새 문서를 빠르게 시작할 수 있는 템플릿과 마법사</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Sjablonen en assistenten maken het begin van nieuwe documenten tot weinig werk</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Szablony i pomocnicy ułatwiający tworzenie nowych dokumentów</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Os modelos e assistentes tornam a criação de documentos novos um esforço mínimo</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Modelos e assistentes permitem criar novos documentos sem esforço</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Šablóny a sprievodcovia robia spúšťanie nových dokumentov veľmi jednoduché</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Predloge in čarovniki omogočajo začetek pisanja novih dokumentov zelo malo dela</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Mallar och guider gör att mycket lite arbete behövs för att påbörja nya dokument</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Şablonlar ve sihirbazlar yeni belgelere başlamayı çok kolaylaştırırlar</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Шаблони і допоміжні засоби для створення документів з мінімальними зусиллями.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxTemplates and wizards make starting new documents very little workxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">模板和向导让创建新文档变得简单高效</li>
      <li>Easy insertion of many standard tags and symbols and the option to define (an arbitrary number of) user defined tags</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">إدراج سهل للعديد من الوسوم والرّموز القياسيّة، إضافة إلى إمكانيّة تعريف المستخدم لوسوم بالعدد الذي يريد</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Inserció fàcil de moltes etiquetes i símbols estàndard, i l'opció de definir (amb un nombre arbitrari) etiquetes definides per l'usuari</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Inserció fàcil de moltes etiquetes i símbols estàndard, i l'opció de definir (amb un nombre arbitrari) etiquetes definides per l'usuari</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Einfaches Einfügen von vielen Standard-Markierungen und -Symbolen und die Möglichkeit zur Definition von einer beliebige Anzahl von benutzerdefinierten Markierungen</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Εύκολη εισαγωγή πολλών τυπικών ετικετών και συμβόλων ακι την επιλογή να καθοριστεί ένα αυθαίρετο πλήθος ετικετών ορισμένων από τον χρήστη</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Easy insertion of many standard tags and symbols and the option to define (an arbitrary number of) user defined tags</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Fácil inserción de numerosas etiquetas y símbolos estándares, además de la opción de definir (cualquier número) de etiquetas del usuario</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Paljude standardsete siltide ja sümbolite hõlpus lisamine ning võimalus defineerida (piiramatul arvul) kasutaja määratud silte</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Etiketa eta ikur estandar asko erraz txertatzea eta erabiltzaileak definitutako etiketak (nahi adina) definitzeko aukera</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Lisää vaivattomasti vakiotunnisteita ja -symboleja sekä määrittele (mielivaltainen määrä) omia tunnisteitasi</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Insertion facile de nombreuses balises et symboles standards avec la possibilité de définir des balises personnalisées</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Inserción fácil de moitas etiquetas e símbolos estándar, e a posibilidade de definir etiquetas de usuario.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Penyisipan mudah banyak tag dan simbol standar dan opsi untuk menentukan (sebuah nomor semaunya) tag yang ditentukan pengguna</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Inserimento semplice di molti tag standard e simboli, inoltre è possibile definire (un numero arbitrario di) tag definiti dall'utente</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">표준 태그와 기호 및 사용자 정의 태그 추가</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Gemakkelijk invoegen van vele standaard tags en symbolen en de optie om (een willekeurig aantal) gebruikergedefinieerde tags te definiëren</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Łatwe wstawianie wielu standardowych znaczników i symboli oraz opcja do definiowania (dowolnej liczby) znaczników użytkownika</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Inserção simples de muitas marcas-padrão e símbolos, assim como a opção para definir (um número arbitrário de) marcas definidas pelo utilizador</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Inserção fácil de várias tags e símbolos comuns, assim como a opção de definir (uma quantidade arbitrária de) tags feitas pelo usuário</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Jednoduché vkladanie mnohých štandardných značiek a symbolov a možnosť definovať (ľubovoľný počet) užívateľom definovaných značiek</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Enostavno vstavljanje številnih standardnih oznak in simbolov ter možnost določitve (poljubno število) uporabniško definiranih oznak</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Enkelt att infoga många standardtaggar och symboler, och möjlighet att definiera (ett godtyckligt antal) användardefinerade taggar</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Pek çok standart etiketin ve sembolün kolayca eklenmesi ve kullanıcı tanımlı etiketleri (isteğe bağlı sayıda) tanımlama seçeneği</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Просте вставлення багатьох стандартних команд і символів, можливість додаткового визначення користувачем довільної кількості команд.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxEasy insertion of many standard tags and symbols and the option to define (an arbitrary number of) user defined tagsxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">简单方便地插入多种标准标签和符号，还对任意数量的用户自定义标签进行定义</li>
      <li>Inverse and forward search: click in the DVI viewer and jump to the corresponding LaTeX line in the editor, or jump from the editor
          to the corresponding page in the viewer</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Cerca directa i inversa: cliqueu en el visualitzador de DVI i salteu a la línia LaTeX corresponent de l'editor, o salteu des de l'editor a la pàgina corresponent en el visualitzador</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Busca directa i inversa: cliqueu en el visor de DVI i salteu a la línia LaTeX corresponent de l'editor, o salteu des de l'editor a la pàgina corresponent en el visor</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Rückwärts- und Vorwärtssuche: Klicken Sie in den DVI-Betrachter und springen Sie zu der entsprechenden LaTeX-Zeile im Editor, oder springen Sie vom Editor zu der entsprechenden Seite im Betrachter</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Αντίστροφη και προς τα εμπρός αναζήτηση: με κλικ στον προβολέα DVI και μετάβαση στη σχετική γραμμή του LaTeX στον επεξεργαστή ή με μετάβαση από τον επεξεργαστή στη σχετική σελίδα στον προβολέα</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Inverse and forward search: click in the DVI viewer and jump to the corresponding LaTeX line in the editor, or jump from the editor to the corresponding page in the viewer</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Búsqueda hacia atrás y hacia adelante: pulse en el visor DVI y vaya a la correspondiente línea de LaTeX en el editor, o vaya del editor a la página correspondiente del visor</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Taasi-ja edasiotsin: klõps DVI näitajas viib vastavale LaTeXi reale redaktoris, redaktorist saab aga samamoodi hüpata vastavale leheküljele näitajas</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Alderantzizko eta aurreranzko bilaketa: egin klik DVI erakuslean eta jauzi editorean dagokion LaTex lerrora, edo egin jauzi editoretik erakuslean dagokion orrira</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Etsi molempiin suuntiin: napsauta DVI-katselinta ja siirry muokkaimessa vastaavalla LaTeX-riville tai siirry muokkaimesta vastaavalle kohtaa katselimessa</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Recherche inversée et en avant : cliquez sur l'afficheur DVI et passez directement à la ligne LaTeX correspondante dans l'éditeur ou passez de l'éditeur à la page correspondante dans l'afficheur</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Busca inversa e cara adiante: prema o visualizador de DVI e salte á liña correspondente de LaTeX no editor, ou salte do editor á páxina correspondente no visualizador.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Pencarian mundur dan maju: klik di DVI viewer dan lompat ke baris LaTeX yang sesuai di editor, atau lompat dari editor ke halaman terkait di viewer</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Ricerca in avanti e indietro: fai clic nel visore DVI per saltare alla riga LaTeX corrispondente nell'editor, oppure salta dalla riga dell'editor alla pagina corrispondente nel visore</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">전방 및 후방 검색: DVI 뷰어에서 항목을 클릭하면 LaTeX 편집기의 해당하는 줄로 이동하며, 그 반대도 가능합니다</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Omgekeerd en voorwaards zoeken: klik in de DVI-viewer en spring naar de overeenkomstige LaTeX regel in de bewerker of spring uit de bewerker naar de overeenkomstige pagina in de viewer</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Wyszukiwanie odwrotne i wprzód: kliknij w przeglądarce DVI i przejdź do odpowiadającego wiersza LaTeX w edytorze lub przejdź z edytora do odpowiadającej strony w przeglądarce</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Pesquisa inversa e directa: carregue no visualizador de DVI e vá para a linha de LaTeX correspondente no editor, ou salte do editor para a página correspondente no visualizador</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Pesquisa inversa e direta: clique no visualizador de DVI e vá para a linha de LaTeX correspondente no editor, ou salte do editor para a página correspondente no visualizador</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Inverzné a predbežné vyhľadávanie: kliknite v prehliadači DVI a prejdite na zodpovedajúcu linku LaTeX v editore alebo prejdite z editora na zodpovedajúcu stránku v prehliadači.</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Iskanje nazaj in naprej: kliknite v pregledovalnik DVI in skok v urejevalnik na ustrezno vrstico v LaTeXu ali skok iz urejevalnika v ustrezno stran v pregledovalniku DVI</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Invers och framåtsökning: Klicka i DVI-visningen och gå till motsvarande Latex-rad i editorn, eller gå från editorn till motsvarande sida i visningen</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Tersine ve ileri arama: DVI görüntüleyiciyi tıklatın ve düzenleyicideki ilgili LaTeX satırına atlayın veya düzenleyiciden görüntüleyicideki ilgili sayfaya atlayın</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Зворотний і прямий пошук: клацання на тексті у програмі для перегляду DVI призведе до переходу до відповідного рядка коду LaTeX у редакторі, а з редактора можна перейти до відповідного місця у програмі для перегляду документів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxInverse and forward search: click in the DVI viewer and jump to the corresponding LaTeX line in the editor, or jump from the editor to the corresponding page in the viewerxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">反向和正向搜索：点击 DVI 查看器即可在编辑器中跳转到对应的 LaTex 代码行，或者点击编辑器代码行跳转到查看器中对应的页面</li>
      <li>Finding chapter or sections is very easy, Kile constructs a list of all the chapter etc. in your document. You can use the list to
          jump to the corresponding section</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">La cerca de capítols o seccions és molt senzilla, El Kile construeix una llista de tots els capítols, etc. en el document. Podeu usar la llista per a saltar a la secció corresponent</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">La busca de capítols o seccions és molt senzilla, Kile construïx una llista de tots els capítols, etc. en el document. Podeu utilitzar la llista per a saltar a la secció corresponent</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Das Auffinden von Kapiteln oder Abschnitten ist sehr einfach, Kile erstellt eine Liste mit allen Kapitel usw. in Ihrem Dokument. Sie können die Liste benutzen, um zu dem entsprechenden Abschnitt zu gehen</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Είναι πολύ εύκολη η εύρεση κεφαλαίων ή ενοτήτων. Το Kile συνθέτει μια λίστα με όλα τα κεφάλαια κλπ. στο έγγραφό σας. Μπορείτε να χρησιμοποιήσετε τη λίστα για να μεταβείτε στη σχετική ενότητα</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Finding chapter or sections is very easy, Kile constructs a list of all the chapter etc. in your document. You can use the list to jump to the corresponding section</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Encontrar capítulos y secciones es muy fácil: Kile construye una lista de todos los capítulos, etc. del documento. Puede usar dicha lista para ir a la sección correspondiente.</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Peatükkide või sektsioonide leidmine on ülimalt lihtne: Kile loob sinu dokumendi kõigi peatükkide, sektsioonide jne nimekirja. Selle abil saab kohe hüpata vajalikku kohta</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Kapituluak edo atalak aurkitzea oso erraza da, Kilek zure dokumentuko kapitulu guztien zerrenda eraikitzen du. Zerrenda erabil dezakezu dagokion atalera pasatzeko</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Löydä (ala-) luku helposti: Kile pitää niistä yllä luetteloa, jonka avulla voit siirtyä luvusta toiseen</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Il n'a jamais été aussi facile de trouver des chapitres ou des sections, Kile construit une liste de tous les chapitres, sections, etc. de vos documents. Vous pouvez utiliser cette liste pour aller directement à la section correspondante.</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Atopar capítulos ou seccións é moi doado, Kile constrúe unha lista de capítulos, etc. no documento. Podes usar a lista para saltar á sección correspondente.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Penemuan bab atau bagian sangat mudah, Kile menyusun daftar semua bab dll. di dokumen Anda. Anda dapat menggunakan daftar untuk melompat ke bagian yang sesuai</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Trovare i capitoli o le sezioni è molto semplice: Kile costruisce un elenco di tutti i capitoli ecc. nel tuo documento, che puoi usare per saltare alla sezione corrispondente</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">문서에 포함된 모든 장과 절을 목록으로 구성하여 쉽게 찾을 수 있습니다. 목록을 통해서 해당하는 부분으로 이동할 수 있습니다</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Vinden van hoofdstuk of sectie is erg gemakkelijk, Kile maakt een lijst met alle hoofdstukken etc. in uw document. U kunt de lijst gebruiken om naar de overeenkomstige sectie te springen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Znajdowanie rozdziałów lub sekcji jest bardzo proste. Kile tworzy listę wszystkich rozdziałów itp. w twoim dokumencie. Możesz uzyć tej listy do przeskakiwania do danej sekcji.</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">A pesquisa de capítulos ou secções é muito simples - o Kile constrói uma lista com todos os capítulos, etc. no seu documento. Poderá usar a lista para ir para a secção correspondente</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Achar o capítulo ou seção correta é muito fácil, o Kile constrói uma lista de todos os capítulos e afins do seu documento, permitindo pular para a seção correspondente rapidamente</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Nájdenie kapitoly alebo odsekov je veľmi jednoduché, Kile zostaví zoznam všetkých kapitol atď. v dokumente. Pomocou tohto zoznamu môžete prejsť na príslušnú časť</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Iskanje poglavja ali poglavij je zelo enostavno, Kile sestavi seznam vseh poglavij itd. v vašem dokumentu. Seznam lahko uporabite za skok naustrezen razdelek</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Det är mycket enkelt att hitta kapitel eller avsnitt. Kile skapar en lista av alla kapitel, etc., i dokumentet. Listan kan användas för att gå till motsvarande avsnitt</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Bölüm veya kısımları bulmak çok kolay, Kile belgenizdeki tüm bölümlerin vb. bir listesini oluşturur. İlgili bölüme atlamak için listeyi kullanabilirsiniz</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Знайти потрібну главу або розділ дуже просто: Kile будує список усіх розділів у документі. Ви можете скористатися цим списком для переходу до відповідного розділу.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFinding chapter or sections is very easy, Kile constructs a list of all the chapter etc. in your document. You can use the list to jump to the corresponding sectionxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">查找章节非常便利，Kile 会构建文档所有章节的列表，您可以使用该列表跳转到对应的章节</li>
      <li>Collect documents that belong together into a project</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">اجمع المستندات ذات العلاقة ببعضها البعض في مشروع</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Reuneix els documents relacionats en un projecte</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Reunix els documents relacionats en un projecte</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Zusammenfassung von zusammengehörigen Dokumenten zu einem Projekt</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Συλλέξτε τα έγγραφα που ανήκουν στο ίδιο έργο</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Collect documents that belong together into a project</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Reunir documentos que deben ir juntos en un proyecto</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Kokkukuuluvate dokumentide koondamine projekti</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Proiektu bati dagozkion dokumentuak biltzea</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Kokoa yhteen kuuluvat tiedostot projektiksi</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Collection de documents appartenant au même projet</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Recolle documentos que van xuntos nun proxecto.</li>
      <li xml:lang="ia">Collige documentos que appertine insimul in un projecto</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Kumpulkan dokumen-dokumen yang menjadi bagian dari suatu projek</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Raccoglie i documenti che appartengono ad un progetto</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">프로젝트에 포함되는 여러 문서 모으기</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Verzamelt documenten die bij elkaar behoren in een project</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Zbieranie dokumentów należących razem do projektu</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Colecção de documentos que pertencem em conjunto a um projecto</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Reúna documentos que pertencem a um mesmo projeto</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Zbierajte dokumenty, ktoré spolu patria do projektu</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Zbere dokumente, ki spadajo skupaj v projekt</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Samla dokument som hör ihop i ett projekt</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Birlikte bir projeye ait olan belgeleri toplayın</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Збирання документів у проєкти.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxCollect documents that belong together into a projectxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">将相互关联的文档集合在同一工程之下进行管理</li>
      <li>Easy insertion of citations and references when using projects</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Inserció fàcil de cites i referències en usar projectes</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Inserció fàcil de cites i referències en utilitzar projectes</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Einfaches Einfügen von Zitaten und Referenzen bei der Verwendung von Projekten</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Εύκολη εισαγωγή παραπομπών και αναφορών με τη χρήση έργων</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Easy insertion of citations and references when using projects</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Fácil inserción de citas y referencias al usar proyectos</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Projektide kasutamisel hõlpus tsitaatide ja viidete lisamine</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Proiektuak erabiltzean aipuak eta erreferentziak erraz sartzea</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Lisää projekteja käytettäessä lainaukset ja viitteet helposti</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Insertion facile de citations et de références au sein de vos projets</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Inserción fácil de citas e referencias ao usar proxectos.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Menyisipkan kutipan dan referensi dengan mudah saat menggunakan projek</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Inserimento semplice di citazioni e di riferimenti quando usi i progetti</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">프로젝트 모드에서 인용과 참고 문헌 간단하게 삽입</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Gemakkelijk invoegen van citaten en referenties bij gebruik van projecten</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Łatwe wstawianie cytowań i odwołań przy użyciu projektów</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Inserção simpless de citações e referências ao usar os projectos</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Inserção fácil de citações e referências ao usar projetos</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Ľahké vkladanie citácií a referencií pri použití projektov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Enostavno vstavljanje citatov in referenc pri uporabi projektov</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Enkelt att infoga hänvisningar och referenser vid användning av projekt</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Projeleri kullanırken alıntıların ve başvuruların kolay eklenmesi</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Просте вставлення посилань у межах проєктів.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxEasy insertion of citations and references when using projectsxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">使用工程时可以轻松插入引用和参考文献</li>
      <li>Flexible and smart build system to compile your LaTeX documents</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">نظام بناء مرن ذكيّ لتصريف مستندات لاتخ</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Sistema de construcció flexible i intel·ligent per a compilar els documents LaTeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Sistema de construcció flexible i intel·ligent per a compilar els documents LaTeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Flexibles und intelligentes Build-System, um Ihre LaTeX-Dokumente zu kompilieren</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Ευέλικτο και έξυπνο σύστημα κατασκευής για μεταγλώττιση των εγγράφων LaTeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Flexible and smart build system to compile your LaTeX documents</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Sistema de construcción flexible e inteligente para compilar documentos LaTeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Paindlik ja nutikas süsteem LaTeXi dokumentide kompileerimiseks</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Zure LaTeX dokumentuak konpilatzeko eraikuntza-sistema malgu eta adimenduna</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Käännä LaTeX-tiedostosi joustavasti ja älykkäästi</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Système de compilation de documents LaTeX flexible et intelligent</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Sistema de construción flexíbel e intelixente para compilar documentos de LaTeX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Sistem pembangunan yang fleksibel dan cerdas untuk mengkompilasi dokumen LaTeX Anda</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Sistema flessibile e intelligente per compilare i tuoi documenti LaTeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">LaTeX 문서를 컴파일할 수 있는 유연하고 똑똑한 빌드 시스템</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Flexibel en slim bouwsysteem om uw LaTeX documenten te compileren</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Eleastyczny i mądry system budowania do kompilowania twoich dokumentów LaTeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Sistema flexível e inteligente de compilação dos seus documentos em LaTeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Sistema de depuração flexível e inteligente para compilar seus documentos do LaTeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Flexibilný a inteligentný systém zostavovania na zostavenie vašich dokumentov LaTeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Fleksibilen in pameten sistem izdelave vaših dokumentov LaTeX</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Flexibelt och smart byggsystem för att kompilera Latex-dokument</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">LaTeX belgelerinizi derlemek için esnek ve akıllı bir inşa sistemi</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Гнучка та інтелектуальна система збирання для обробки ваших документів LaTeX.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxFlexible and smart build system to compile your LaTeX documentsxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">灵活且智能的构建系统，方便您对 LaTex 文档进行编译</li>
      <li>QuickPreview: preview a selected part of your document</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">المعاينة السّريعة: عاين جزءًا من مستندك</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">QuickPreview: vista prèvia d'una part seleccionada del document</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">QuickPreview: vista prèvia d'una part seleccionada del document</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Schnellvorschau: Vorschau eines ausgewählten Teils eines Dokuments</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">QuickPreview: προεπισκόπηση ενός επιλεγμένου τμήματος του εγγράφου σας</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">QuickPreview: preview a selected part of your document</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Vista rápida: vista previa de la parte seleccionada del documento</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Kiireelvaade: dokumendi valitud osa eelvaatlus</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Aurreikuspegi azkarra: aurreikusi zure dokumentuan hautatutako zati bat</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Esikatsele nopeasti tiedoston valittua osa pikaesikatselulla</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Aperçu rapide : aperçu rapide d'un passage sélectionné de votre document</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Previsualización da parte seleccionada dun documento.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">QuickPreview: mempratinjau bagian yang dipilih dari dokumen Anda</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Anteprima rapida: anteprima di una parte selezionata del tuo documento</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">빠른 미리 보기: 문서의 선택한 부분 미리 보기</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">QuickPreview: bekijk een geselecteerd deel van uw document</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">SzybkiPodgląd: podgląd wybranej części dokumentu</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Antevisão Rápida: antevisão de uma parte seleccionada do seu documento</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Visualização rápida: pré-visualize uma parte específica do seu documento</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">QuickPreview: ukážka vybranej časti dokumentu</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">QuickPreview: predogled izbranega dela dokumenta</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Snabbgranskning: Förhandsgranska en markerad del av dokumentet</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">QuickPreview: belgenizin seçili bir bölümünü önizleyin</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Швидкий перегляд: можливість швидко переглянути частину вашого документа.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxQuickPreview: preview a selected part of your documentxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">快速预览：预览文档中选中的部分</li>
      <li>Easy access to various help sources</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">وصول سهل إلى مختلف مصادر المساعدة</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Accés fàcil a diverses fonts d'ajuda</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Accés fàcil a diverses fonts d'ajuda</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Einfacher Zugang zu verschiedenen Hilfsquellen</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Εύκολη πρόσβαση σε διάφορες πηγές βοήθειας</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Easy access to various help sources</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Fácil acceso a diversas fuentes de ayuda</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Hõlpus ligipääs paljudele abistavatele allikatele</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Hainbat laguntza-iturri eskura izatea</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Löydä eri lähteiden ohjeet nopeasti</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Accès rapide à de nombreuses sources d'assistance</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Acceso doado a varios recursos de axuda.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Akses mudah untuk berbagai sumberdaya bantuan</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Semplice accesso a varie risorse di aiuto</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">여러 도움말 정보에 쉽게 접근</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Gemakkelijke toegang tot verschillende hulpbronnen</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Łatwy dostęp do źródeł pomocy</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Acesso simples a diversas fontes de ajuda</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Acesso fácil a várias fontes de ajuda</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Ľahký prístup k rôznym zdrojom pomoci</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Enostaven dostop do različnih virov pomoči</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Enkel tillgång till olika hjälpkällor</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">Çeşitli yardım kaynaklarına kolay erişim</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Простий доступ до різноманітних довідкових джерел.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxEasy access to various help sourcesxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">轻松访问各种帮助资源</li>
      <li>Advanced editing commands</li>
      <li xml:lang="ar">أوامر تحرير متقدّمة</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca">Edició avançada d'ordres</li>
      <li xml:lang="ca-valencia">Edició avançada d'ordres</li>
      <li xml:lang="de">Erweiterte Bearbeitungsbefehle</li>
      <li xml:lang="el">Προηγμένες εντολές επεξεργασίας</li>
      <li xml:lang="en-GB">Advanced editing commands</li>
      <li xml:lang="es">Órdenes de edición avanzadas</li>
      <li xml:lang="et">Rohked muutmiskäsud</li>
      <li xml:lang="eu">Edizio-komando aurreratuak</li>
      <li xml:lang="fi">Kehittyneet muokkauskomennot</li>
      <li xml:lang="fr">Commandes d'édition avancées</li>
      <li xml:lang="gl">Ordes de edición avanazda.</li>
      <li xml:lang="id">Perintah pengeditan tingkat-lanjut</li>
      <li xml:lang="it">Comandi di modifica avanzati</li>
      <li xml:lang="ka">რედაქტორის დამატებითი ბრძანებები</li>
      <li xml:lang="ko">고급 편집 명령</li>
      <li xml:lang="nl">Geavanceerde commando's voor bewerking</li>
      <li xml:lang="pl">Rozszerzone polecenia edytowania</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt">Comandos de edição avançados</li>
      <li xml:lang="pt-BR">Comandos de edição avançados</li>
      <li xml:lang="sk">Rozšírené editovacie príkazy</li>
      <li xml:lang="sl">Napredni ukazi za urejanje</li>
      <li xml:lang="sv">Avancerade redigeringskommandon</li>
      <li xml:lang="tr">İleri düzey düzenleme komutları</li>
      <li xml:lang="uk">Розширені команди редагування.</li>
      <li xml:lang="x-test">xxAdvanced editing commandsxx</li>
      <li xml:lang="zh-CN">高级编辑命令</li>
    </ul>
  </description>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Document editing in Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca">Edició d'un document al Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ca-valencia">Edició d'un document a Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="cs">Vytváření dokumentu v Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="de">Bearbeitung eines Dokuments in Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="el">Επεξεργασία εγγράφων στο Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="en-GB">Document editing in Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Edición de documentos en Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="et">Dokumendi redigeerimine Kiles</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="eu">Dokumentuak Kilen editatzea</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fi">Tiedoston muokkaus Kilessä</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="fr">Édition de documents dans Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="gl">Edición de documentos en Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="id">Pengeditan dokumen di Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="it">Modifica dei documenti in Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ka">დოკუმენტს ჩასწორება Kile-ში</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="ko">Kile로 문서 편집</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Bewerking van documenten in Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pl">Edytowanie dokumentów w Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Edição de documentos no Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt-BR">Edição de documentos no Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sk">Úpravy dokumentov v Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sl">Urejanje dokumentov v Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Dokumentredigering i Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="tr">Kile'de belge düzenleme</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Редагування документа у Kile</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxDocument editing in Kilexx</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="zh-CN">Kile 文档编辑</caption>
      <image>https://cdn.kde.org/screenshots/kile/kile.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <url type="homepage">https://kile.sourceforge.io</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=kile</url>
  <url type="help">https://docs.kde.org/?application=kile</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>kile</binary>
  </provides>
  <custom>
    <value key="KDE::windows_store">https://www.microsoft.com/store/apps/9PMBNG78PFK3</value>
  </custom>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <releases>
    <release version="3.0b4" date="2022-01-03"/>
    <release version="3.0b3" date="2019-11-10"/>
    <release version="3.0b2" date="2018-05-19"/>
    <release version="3.0b1" date="2017-09-30"/>
  </releases>
</component>
